the sriram group has indicated that it
is looking to bring in new investors
like kkr into its insurance businesses
which will be the major focus segments
for the group in the coming decade
both our general and life insurance
companies are doing well and are
profitable
they don't need any capital per se
also sriram capital can use that money
for other purposes like increasing the
shareholding managing director sriram
transport finance company umesh revenker
who will be one of the four members of
board of management of the group told
businessline
currently the company is scouting for
new investors for the general insurance
business in which sriram capital has
76.63 percent stake while san lam
emerging markets ltd holds 22.92 percent
the due diligence process is still on
we will soon finalize the deal he added
according to industry players isis
lombard general insurance was valued 40
times its pat while new india assurance
had a valuation of 22 times its pat